



Summary

I'm Pourya Dehghan a Software engineer with the background of petrochemical engineering educations and designing experience. I started my coding journey two years ago, I feel really lucky that my job is my biggest hobby. I'm eager to make the leap and continue refining my skills with the right company.

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, React, React Native, Django, MongoDB, Boostrap, PostgreSQL, Github, Photoshop, Lightroom

Education and Training

General Assembly Remote Software Engineer

Bachelor of Science Marvdasht Azad University Petrochemical Engineering, 2013

Experience

General Assembly

Software Engineer | Remote 05/2021 to 08/2021

Learning programming and computer science fundamentals, and creating full stack applications.

Uber

Driver | Atlanta, GA 04/2017 to 06/2021

Yerce

Photo Editor & Designer | Turkey 06/2014 to 12/2016
Photographer
Designing Wedding albums.

Languages

English Persian

Turkish

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.pouryadegan.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/degan90
- https://github.com/Degan90